In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, the
market cap of the company is
and if we talk about the positive point in the company then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
profit of the company has also increased in the quarters
and the promoter's wedding [sangeet] was done in the share holding, at
this time a
discount of 25% is being given from the above level, so if you
want to buy in this company then you
can start buying from the level of ₹1200, that's all in this video, if you liked the
information given in the video then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to our channel